Guide to the William Benton Papers 1839-1973
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Speech Files
  Yale Conference, summary by members of President's Committee, 2/3-4/58; #152F
  Yale Conference, transcript, 2/3-4/58; #152R
  Yale Conference, Benton speech, "Pace of Change," 2/3-4/58; #152H
  Yale Conference, Bevis speech, "Soviet Scientific Challenge," 2/3-4/58; #152I
  Yale Conference, Dubridge speech, "Education in the Age of Science," 2/3-4/58; #152J
  Yale Conference, Dulles speech, "Soviet Challenge; Science and Technology," 2/3-4/58; #152K
  Yale Conference, Killian speech, "Toward a New Level of Excellence; Education in Science," 2/3-4/58; #152L
  Yale Conference, McBride speech, "Education," 2/3-4/58; #152M
  Yale Conference, Meyer speech, "Educating Future Scientists in a Rounded Educational System," 2/3-4/58; #152N
  Yale Conference, Waterman speech, "Soviet Challenge; Science," 2/3-4/58; #1520
  Yale Conference, television, 2/2/58; #160
  Yale Conference, television, Benton and scientists interviewed, 1/31/58; #175
  Yale University, photo, Benton family at 35th reunion Class of 1921, 6/56; #1449
  Yale University, photo, 30th reunion of Class of 1921, 6/51; #1539
  Yntema, Ted, photo, autographed; #1417
  Zaiman, Jack, "Needle's Eye; Cheapest Vacation," Hartford Courant, 9/59; #1290
  Zaiman, "Senate Fight; Democrats Shaken by Intensity," ibid., 6/29/58; #837A
  Zaiman, radio, "Senatorial Nomination," 5/14/58; #940
  - 1 (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - 2 (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - 3 (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - 4 (Box 449, Folder 4)
  - 5 (Box 449, Folder 5)
  - 6 (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - 7 (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - 8.1 (Box 449, Folder 8)
  - 8.2 (Box 449, Folder 9)
  - 9 (Box 449, Folder 10)
  - 10 (Box 449, Folder 11)
  - 11 (Box 449, Folder 12)
  - 12 (Box 449, Folder 13)
  - 13.1 (Box 449, Folder 14)
  - 13.2 (Box 449, Folder 15)
  - 14 (Box 449, Folder 16)
  - 15 (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - 16 (Box 450, Folder 2)
  - 17 (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - 18 (Box 450, Folder 4)
  - 19 (Box 450, Folder 5)
  - 20-21 (Box 450, Folder 6)
  - 22 (Box 450, Folder 7)
  - 23 (Box 450, Folder 8)
  - 24 (Box 450, Folder 9)
  - 25 (Box 450, Folder 10)
  - 26 (Box 450, Folder 11)
  - 27 (Box 450, Folder 12)
  - 28 (Box 450, Folder 13)
  - 29 (Box 450, Folder 14)
  - 30 (Box 450, Folder 15)
  - 31.1 (Box 451, Folder 1)
  - 31.2 (Box 451, Folder 2)
  - 31.3 (Box 451, Folder 3)
  - 31.4 (Box 451, Folder 4)
  - 31.5 (Box 451, Folder 5)
  - 31.6 (Box 451, Folder 6)
  - 31.7 (Box 451, Folder 7)
  - 32 (Box 452, Folder 1)
  - 33 (Box 452, Folder 2)
  - 34 (Box 452, Folder 3)
  - 35 (Box 452, Folder 4)
  - 36 (Box 452, Folder 5)
  - 37 (Box 452, Folder 6)
  - 38 (Box 452, Folder 7)
  - 39 (Box 452, Folder 8)
  - 39A (Box 452, Folder 9)
  - 39B (Box 452, Folder 10)
  - 39C (Box 452, Folder 11)
  - 40 (Box 452, Folder 12)
  - 41 (Box 452, Folder 13)
  - 42 (Box 453, Folder 1)
  - 42A (Box 453, Folder 2)
  - 42C (Box 453, Folder 3)
  - 43 (Box 453, Folder 4)
  - 44 (Box 453, Folder 5)
  - 45 (Box 453, Folder 6)
  - 46 (Box 453, Folder 7)
  - 47 (Box 453, Folder 8)
  - 48 (Box 453, Folder 9)
  - 49 (Box 453, Folder 10)
  - 50 (Box 453, Folder 11)
  - 51 (Box 453, Folder 12)
  - 52 (Box 453, Folder 13)
  - 53 (Box 453, Folder 14)
  - 54 (Box 453, Folder 15)
  - 55.1 (Box 453, Folder 16)
  - 55.2 (Box 453, Folder 17)
  - 55.3 (Box 453, Folder 18)
  - 55A (Box 454, Folder 1)
  - 56 (Box 454, Folder 2)
  - 57 (Box 454, Folder 3)
  - 58 (Box 454, Folder 4)
  - 59 (Box 454, Folder 5)
  - 60 (Box 454, Folder 6)
  - 61 (Box 454, Folder 7)
  - 62 (Box 454, Folder 8)
  - 63 (Box 454, Folder 9)
  - 64 (Box 454, Folder 10)
  - 65 (Box 454, Folder 11)
  - 66 (Box 454, Folder 12)
  - 67 (Box 454, Folder 13)
  - 68.1 (Box 455, Folder 1)
  - 68.2 (Box 455, Folder 2)
  - 68C (Box 455, Folder 3)
  - 69 (Box 455, Folder 4)
  - 70 (Box 455, Folder 5)
  - 71 (Box 455, Folder 6)
  - 72 (Box 455, Folder 7)
  - 73 (Box 455, Folder 8)
  - 74 (Box 455, Folder 9)
  - 75 (Box 455, Folder 10)
  - 76 (Box 455, Folder 11)
  - 77 (Box 455, Folder 12)
  - 78 (Box 455, Folder 13)
  - 79 (Box 455, Folder 14)
  - 80 (Box 455, Folder 15)
  - 81 (Box 455, Folder 16)
  - 82 (Box 455, Folder 17)
  - 83 (Box 455, Folder 18)
  - 84 (Box 455, Folder 19)
  - 85 (Box 456, Folder 1)
  - 86 (Box 456, Folder 2)
  - 87 (Box 456, Folder 3)
  - 87A (Box 456, Folder 4)
  - 88 (Box 456, Folder 5)
  - 89 (Box 456, Folder 6)
  - 90 (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - 91 (Box 456, Folder 8)
  - 92 (Box 456, Folder 9)
  - 93 (Box 456, Folder 10)
  - 94 (Box 456, Folder 11)
  - 95 (Box 456, Folder 12)
  - 96 (Box 456, Folder 13)
  - 97 (Box 456, Folder 14)
  - 98 (Box 456, Folder 15)
  - 99 (Box 456, Folder 16)
  - 100 (Box 456, Folder 17)
  - 101 (Box 456, Folder 18)
  - 102 (Box 456, Folder 19)
  - 103 (Box 456, Folder 20)
  - 104 (Box 456, Folder 21)
  - 104A (Box 456, Folder 22)
  - 104B-104C (Box 457, Folder 1)
  - 105-106 (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - 107 (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - 108 (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - 110 (Box 457, Folder 5)
  - 111 (Box 457, Folder 6)
  - 112 (Box 457, Folder 7)
  - 113.1 (Box 458, Folder 1)
  - 113.2 (Box 458, Folder 2)
  - 113.3 (Box 458, Folder 3)
  - 113.4 (Box 458, Folder 4)
  - 113A (Box 458, Folder 5)
  - 113B (Box 458, Folder 6)
  - 113C (Box 458, Folder 7)
  - 113D (Box 458, Folder 8)
  - 114 (Box 459, Folder 1)
  - 115 (Box 459, Folder 2)
  - 116 (Box 459, Folder 3)
  - 117 (Box 459, Folder 4)
  - 118 (Box 459, Folder 5)
  - 119 (Box 459, Folder 6)
  - 120 (Box 459, Folder 7)
  - 122 (Box 459, Folder 8)
  - 123 (Box 459, Folder 9)
  - 124 (Box 459, Folder 10)
  - 125 (Box 459, Folder 11)
  - 126 (Box 459, Folder 12)
  - 127 (Box 459, Folder 13)
  - 128 (Box 459, Folder 14)
  - 129 (Box 459, Folder 15)
  - 130 (Box 459, Folder 16)
  - 131 (Box 459, Folder 17)
  - 132 (Box 459, Folder 18)
  - 133 (Box 459, Folder 19)
  - 134 (Box 459, Folder 20)
  - 135 (Box 459, Folder 21)
  - 136 (Box 459, Folder 22)
  - 137 (Box 459, Folder 23)
  - 138 (Box 459, Folder 24)
  - 139 (Box 459, Folder 25)
  - 140 (Box 459, Folder 26)
  - 141 (Box 460, Folder 1)
  - 142.1 (Box 460, Folder 2)
  - 142.2 (Box 460, Folder 3)
  - 142.3 (Box 460, Folder 4)
  - 142A (Box 460, Folder 5)
  - 143 (Box 460, Folder 6)
  - 144 (Box 460, Folder 7)
  - 145 (Box 460, Folder 8)
  - 146 (Box 460, Folder 9)
  - 147 (Box 460, Folder 10)
  - 148 (Box 460, Folder 11)
  - 149 (Box 460, Folder 12)
  - 150 (Box 460, Folder 13)
  - 151 (Box 460, Folder 14)
  - 151A (Box 460, Folder 15)
  - 151B (Box 460, Folder 16)
  - 151C-151K (Box 460, Folder 17)
  - 152.1 (Box 461, Folder 1)
  - 152.2 (Box 461, Folder 2)
  - 152A-152E (Box 461, Folder 3)
  - 142F-142P (Box 461, Folder 4)
  - 152R (Box 461, Folder 5)
  - 152S-152U (Box 461, Folder 6)
  - 153 (Box 461, Folder 7)
  - 154-158 (Box 462, Folder 1)
  - 159 (Box 462, Folder 2)
  - 160 (Box 462, Folder 3)
  - 161 (Box 462, Folder 4)
  - 162 (Box 462, Folder 5)
  - 163 (Box 462, Folder 6)
  - 163A (Box 462, Folder 7)
  - 163B (Box 462, Folder 8)
  - 163C (Box 462, Folder 9)
  - 163D (Box 462, Folder 10)
  - 163E (Box 462, Folder 11)
  - 163F (Box 462, Folder 12)
  - 163G (Box 462, Folder 13)
  - 163H (Box 462, Folder 14)
  - 164 (Box 462, Folder 15)
  - 165 (Box 462, Folder 16)
  - 166 (Box 462, Folder 17)
  - 167 (Box 462, Folder 18)
  - 168 (Box 462, Folder 19)
  - 169 (Box 462, Folder 20)
  - 170 (Box 462, Folder 21)
  - 171 (Box 462, Folder 22)
  - 172 (Box 463, Folder 1)
  - 172A (Box 463, Folder 2)
  - 173 (Box 463, Folder 3)
  - 174 (Box 463, Folder 4)
  - 175 (Box 463, Folder 5)
  - 176 (Box 463, Folder 6)
  - 177-178 (Box 463, Folder 7)
  - 179 (Box 463, Folder 8)
  - 180 (Box 463, Folder 9)
  - 181.1 (Box 463, Folder 10)
  - 181.2 (Box 463, Folder 11)
  - 181.3 (Box 464, Folder 1)
  - 181.4 (Box 464, Folder 2)
  - 182-183 (Box 464, Folder 3)
  - 184 (Box 464, Folder 4)
  - 185 (Box 464, Folder 5)
  - 186-190 (Box 464, Folder 6)
  - 191 (Box 464, Folder 7)
  - 192 (Box 464, Folder 8)
  - 193-195 (Box 464, Folder 9)
  - 196 (Box 464, Folder 10)
  - 197-200 (Box 464, Folder 11)
  - 201 (Box 464, Folder 12)
  - 202 (Box 464, Folder 13)
  - 203 (Box 464, Folder 14)
  - 204 (Box 464, Folder 15)
  - 205-207 (Box 464, Folder 16)
  - 208 (Box 465, Folder 1)
  - 208A (Box 465, Folder 2)
  - 208B-208E (Box 465, Folder 3)
  - 209-210 (Box 465, Folder 4)
  - 211 (Box 465, Folder 5)
  - 212-212A (Box 465, Folder 6)
  - 213 (Box 465, Folder 7)
  - 214-215 (Box 465, Folder 8)
  - 216-218 (Box 465, Folder 9)
  - 219 (Box 465, Folder 10)
  - 220 (Box 465, Folder 11)
  - 221-224 (Box 465, Folder 12)
  - 225 (Box 465, Folder 13)
  - 226 (Box 465, Folder 14)
  - 227 (Box 465, Folder 15)
  - 228-229 (Box 465, Folder 16)
  - 230 (Box 466, Folder 1)
  - 231 (Box 466, Folder 2)
  - 232 (Box 466, Folder 3)
  - 233 (Box 466, Folder 4)
  - 234 (Box 466, Folder 5)
  - 235 (Box 466, Folder 6)
  - 236 (Box 466, Folder 7)
  - 237 (Box 466, Folder 8)
  - 238 (Box 466, Folder 9)
  - 239 (Box 466, Folder 10)
  - 240 (Box 466, Folder 11)
  - 241 (Box 466, Folder 12)
  - 242 (Box 466, Folder 13)
  - 243 (Box 466, Folder 14)
  - 244 (Box 466, Folder 15)
  - 245 (Box 466, Folder 16)
  - 245A (Box 466, Folder 17)
  - 246 (Box 466, Folder 18)
  - 247 (Box 466, Folder 19)
  - 248 (Box 466, Folder 20)
  - 249 (Box 466, Folder 21)
  - 250 (Box 466, Folder 22)
  - 251 (Box 466, Folder 23)
  - 252 (Box 466, Folder 24)
  - 253 (Box 466, Folder 25)
  - 254-256 (Box 466, Folder 26)
  - 257 (Box 467, Folder 1)
  - 258 (Box 467, Folder 2)
  - 259 (Box 467, Folder 3)
  - 259A (Box 467, Folder 4)
  - 259B (Box 467, Folder 5)
  - 259C (Box 467, Folder 6)
  - 260 (Box 467, Folder 7)
  - 261 (Box 467, Folder 8)
  - 262 (Box 467, Folder 9)
  - 263 (Box 467, Folder 10)
  - 264 (Box 467, Folder 11)
  - 265 (Box 467, Folder 12)
  - 266 (Box 467, Folder 13)
  - 267 (Box 467, Folder 14)
  - 268 (Box 467, Folder 15)
  - 269 (Box 467, Folder 16)
  - 270 (Box 467, Folder 17)
  - 271 (Box 467, Folder 18)
  - 272 (Box 467, Folder 19)
  - 273 (Box 467, Folder 20)
  - 274 (Box 467, Folder 21)
  - 275 (Box 467, Folder 22)
  - 276 (Box 467, Folder 23)
  - 277 (Box 468, Folder 1)
  - 278 (Box 468, Folder 2)
  - 279 (Box 468, Folder 3)
  - 280A-280B (Box 468, Folder 4)
  - 281 (Box 468, Folder 5)
  - 282.1 (Box 469, Folder 1)
  - 282.2 (Box 469, Folder 2)
  - 282.3 (Box 469, Folder 3)
  - 282.4 (Box 469, Folder 4)
  - 282.5 (Box 469, Folder 5)
  - 282.6 (Box 469, Folder 6)
  - 282.7 (Box 469, Folder 7)
  - 282.8 (Box 469, Folder 8)
  - 282.9 (Box 469, Folder 9)
  - 282A (Box 469, Folder 10)
  - 283 (Box 469, Folder 11)
  - 284.1 (Box 470, Folder 1)
  - 284.2 (Box 470, Folder 2)
  - 284.3 (Box 470, Folder 3)
  - 284.4 (Box 470, Folder 4)
  - 284.5 (Box 470, Folder 5)
  - 284.6 (Box 470, Folder 6)
  - 284.7 (Box 470, Folder 7)
  - 284.8 (Box 470, Folder 8)
  - 284.9 (Box 470, Folder 9)
  - 284.10 (Box 470, Folder 10)
  - 284A (Box 470, Folder 11)
  - 284B (Box 470, Folder 12)
  - 285 (Box 471, Folder 1)
  - 285A (Box 471, Folder 2)
  - 286 (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - 287 (Box 471, Folder 4)
  - 288 (Box 471, Folder 5)
  - 289 (Box 471, Folder 6)
  - 290-291 (Box 471, Folder 7)
  - 292.1 (Box 472, Folder 1)
  - 292.2 (Box 472, Folder 2)
  - 292.3 (Box 472, Folder 3)
  - 292.4 (Box 472, Folder 4)
  - 292.5 (Box 472, Folder 5)
  - 292.6 (Box 472, Folder 6)
  - 292.7 (Box 472, Folder 7)
  - 292.8 (Box 472, Folder 8)
  - 292.9 (Box 472, Folder 9)
  - 292.10 (Box 473, Folder 1)
  - 292.11 (Box 473, Folder 2)
  - 292.12 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - 292.13 (Box 473, Folder 4)
  - 292.14 (Box 473, Folder 5)
  - 292.15 (Box 473, Folder 6)
  - 292.16 (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - 292.17 (Box 473, Folder 8)
  - 292A (Box 473, Folder 9)
  - 292B.1 (Box 473, Folder 10)
  - 292B.2 (Box 473, Folder 11)
  - 292C (Box 473, Folder 12)
  - 292D (Box 473, Folder 13)
  - 293-296 (Box 474, Folder 1)
  - 297-300 (Box 474, Folder 2)
  - 300A-300C (Box 474, Folder 3)
  - 300D-300I (Box 474, Folder 4)
  - 301-304 (Box 474, Folder 5)
  - 305 (Box 474, Folder 6)
  - 306-307A (Box 474, Folder 7)
  - 308-309A (Box 474, Folder 8)
  - 310-311 (Box 474, Folder 9)
  - 312-314 (Box 474, Folder 10)
  - 315-317 (Box 474, Folder 11)
  - 318-321 (Box 474, Folder 12)
  - 322-324 (Box 474, Folder 13)
  - 325 (Box 474, Folder 14)
  - 326 (Box 474, Folder 15)
  - 327-327A (Box 474, Folder 16)
  - 328-329 (Box 474, Folder 17)
  - 330-339 (Box 475, Folder 1)
  - 340-343 (Box 475, Folder 2)
  - 344 (Box 475, Folder 3)
  - 345-349 (Box 475, Folder 4)
  - 350-352 (Box 475, Folder 5)
  - 353-356 (Box 475, Folder 6)
  - 357-361B (Box 475, Folder 7)
  - 362-363B (Box 475, Folder 8)
  - 364 (Box 475, Folder 9)
  - 365A-367 (Box 475, Folder 10)
  - 368 (Box 475, Folder 11)
  - 369 (Box 475, Folder 12)
  - 370 (Box 475, Folder 13)
  - 371-372 (Box 475, Folder 14)
  - 373 (Box 475, Folder 15)
  - 374-381 (Box 475, Folder 16)
  - 382 (Box 475, Folder 17)
  - 383-384 (Box 475, Folder 18)
  - 385 (Box 475, Folder 19)
  - 386-390 (Box 475, Folder 20)
  - 391 (Box 475, Folder 21)
  - 391A-392 (Box 476, Folder 1)
  - 393 (Box 476, Folder 2)
  - 394 (Box 476, Folder 3)
  - 395-396 (Box 476, Folder 4)
  - 397-400 (Box 476, Folder 5)
  - 401 (Box 476, Folder 6)
  - 403-406 (Box 476, Folder 7)
  - 407-414 (Box 476, Folder 8)
  - 415-416 (Box 476, Folder 9)
  - 417 (Box 476, Folder 10)
  - 418-421 (Box 476, Folder 11)
  - 422-425 (Box 476, Folder 12)
  - 426-430 (Box 476, Folder 13)
  - 431 (Box 476, Folder 14)
  - 432-433 (Box 477, Folder 1)
  - 434-437 (Box 477, Folder 2)
  - 438-440 (Box 477, Folder 3)
  - 441-445 (Box 477, Folder 4)
  - 446-448A (Box 477, Folder 5)
  - 449 (Box 477, Folder 6)
  - 450-451 (Box 477, Folder 7)
  - 452 (Box 477, Folder 8)
  - 453-454A (Box 477, Folder 9)
  - 455-457A (Box 477, Folder 10)
  - 458-459 (Box 477, Folder 11)
  - 460-465 (Box 477, Folder 12)
  - 466-470 (Box 477, Folder 13)
  - 471 (Box 477, Folder 14)
  - 472-475 (Box 478, Folder 1)
  - 476 (Box 478, Folder 2)
  - 477 (Box 478, Folder 3)
  - 478 (Box 478, Folder 4)
  - 478A-478B (Box 478, Folder 5)
  - 479 (Box 478, Folder 6)
  - 480-481 (Box 478, Folder 7)
  - 482-483A (Box 478, Folder 8)
  - 484-490 (Box 478, Folder 9)
  - 491-493 (Box 478, Folder 10)
  - 494 (Box 478, Folder 11)
  - 495-497 (Box 478, Folder 12)
  - 498-499 (Box 478, Folder 13)
  - 500-500A (Box 479, Folder 1)
  - 501-503 (Box 479, Folder 2)
  - 504-506 (Box 479, Folder 3)
  - 506A (Box 479, Folder 4)
  - 507-511A (Box 479, Folder 5)
  - 512 (Box 479, Folder 6)
  - 513-516 (Box 479, Folder 7)
  - 517-518 (Box 479, Folder 8)
  - 519-519A (Box 479, Folder 9)
  - 520 (Box 479, Folder 10)
  - 521-525 (Box 479, Folder 11)
  - 526 (Box 480, Folder 1)
  - 526A (Box 480, Folder 2)
  - 527 (Box 480, Folder 3)
  - 528 (Box 480, Folder 4)
  - 528B (Box 480, Folder 5)
  - 528C-528D (Box 480, Folder 6)
  - 528E (Box 480, Folder 7)
  - 529 (Box 480, Folder 8)
  - 530-536 (Box 480, Folder 9)
  - 537-540 (Box 480, Folder 10)
  - 541-542 (Box 480, Folder 11)
  - 542A-546 (Box 480, Folder 12)
  - 547 (Box 480, Folder 13)
  - 548 (Box 481, Folder 1)
  - 548.1 (Box 481, Folder 2)
  - 549-551 (Box 481, Folder 3)
  - 552 (Box 481, Folder 4)
  - 553-554 (Box 481, Folder 5)
  - 555 (Box 481, Folder 6)
  - 556-559 (Box 481, Folder 7)
  - 560-564 (Box 481, Folder 8)
  - 565-566 (Box 481, Folder 9)
  - 567 (Box 481, Folder 10)
  - 568-569E (Box 481, Folder 11)
  - 570-574 (Box 481, Folder 12)
  - 575-582 (Box 482, Folder 1)
  - 583-584 (Box 482, Folder 2)
  - 585 (Box 482, Folder 3)
  - 586 (Box 482, Folder 4)
  - 587-588 (Box 482, Folder 5)
  - 589.1 (Box 482, Folder 6)
  - 589.2 (Box 482, Folder 7)
  - 589.3 (Box 482, Folder 8)
  - 590-592 (Box 482, Folder 9)
  - 593 (Box 482, Folder 10)
  - 594-599 (Box 482, Folder 11)
  - 600-603 (Box 482, Folder 12)
  - 604-607 (Box 482, Folder 13)
  - 608 (Box 482, Folder 14)
  - 609-611 (Box 483, Folder 1)
  - 612 (Box 483, Folder 2)
  - 613-614 (Box 483, Folder 3)
  - 615.1 (Box 483, Folder 4)
  - 615.2 (Box 483, Folder 5)
  - 616-619 (Box 483, Folder 6)
  - 620-623 (Box 483, Folder 7)
  - 624-627 (Box 483, Folder 8)
  - 628-629 (Box 483, Folder 9)
  - 630-631 (Box 484, Folder 1)
  - 632 (Box 484, Folder 2)
  - 632A (Box 484, Folder 3)
  - 633.1 (Box 484, Folder 4)
  - 633.2 (Box 484, Folder 5)
  - 633A (Box 484, Folder 6)
  - 633B (Box 484, Folder 7)
  - 633C (Box 484, Folder 8)
  - 633D-633F (Box 484, Folder 9)
  - 634 (Box 484, Folder 10)
  - 635-637 (Box 484, Folder 11)
  - 638 (Box 484, Folder 12)
  - 639 (Box 484, Folder 13)
  - 640-640A (Box 484, Folder 14)
  - 641 (Box 484, Folder 15)
  - 642 (Box 484, Folder 16)
  - 642A-642B (Box 484, Folder 17)
  - 643-644 (Box 484, Folder 18)
  - 645 (Box 484, Folder 19)
  - 646 (Box 484, Folder 20)
  - 647-648 (Box 485, Folder 1)
  - 649 (Box 485, Folder 2)
  - 650 (Box 485, Folder 3)
  - 651 (Box 485, Folder 4)
  - 652-654 (Box 485, Folder 5)
  - 655 (Box 485, Folder 6)
  - 656 (Box 485, Folder 7)
  - 657 (Box 485, Folder 8)
  - 658-658A (Box 485, Folder 9)
  - 659 (Box 485, Folder 10)
  - 660-660A (Box 485, Folder 11)
  - 661-662 (Box 485, Folder 12)
  - 663-663A (Box 485, Folder 13)
  - 664 (Box 485, Folder 14)
  - 665 (Box 485, Folder 15)
  - 666-667 (Box 485, Folder 16)
  - 668 (Box 485, Folder 17)
  - 669 (Box 485, Folder 18)
  - 670-673 (Box 486, Folder 1)
  - 674-676 (Box 486, Folder 2)
  - 677-678 (Box 486, Folder 3)
  - 679-679A (Box 486, Folder 4)
  - 680 (Box 486, Folder 5)
  - 681-684 (Box 486, Folder 6)
  - 685-685A (Box 486, Folder 7)
  - 686-688 (Box 486, Folder 8)
  - 689-689A (Box 486, Folder 9)
  - 690-693 (Box 486, Folder 10)
  - 694-699 (Box 486, Folder 11)
  - 700-702 (Box 486, Folder 12)
  - 703-705 (Box 487, Folder 1)
  - 706-709 (Box 487, Folder 2)
  - 710-713 (Box 487, Folder 3)
  - 714 (Box 487, Folder 4)
  - 715-719 (Box 487, Folder 5)
  - 720-724 (Box 487, Folder 6)
  - 725.1 (Box 487, Folder 7)
  - 725.2 (Box 487, Folder 8)
  - 726 (Box 487, Folder 9)
  - 727.1 (Box 487, Folder 10)
  - 727.2 (Box 487, Folder 11)
  - 728 (Box 487, Folder 12)
  - 729-731 (Box 487, Folder 13)
  - 732-734 (Box 487, Folder 14)
  - 735-736 (Box 488, Folder 1)
  - 737-739 (Box 488, Folder 2)
  - 740-741 (Box 488, Folder 3)
  - 742-743 (Box 488, Folder 4)
  - 744-745 (Box 488, Folder 5)
  - 746-749 (Box 488, Folder 6)
  - 750-751 (Box 488, Folder 7)
  - 752.1 (Box 488, Folder 8)
  - 752.2 (Box 488, Folder 9)
  - 753-756 (Box 488, Folder 10)
  - 757-758 (Box 488, Folder 11)
  - 759 (Box 489, Folder 1)
  - 760-761 (Box 489, Folder 2)
  - 762-765 (Box 489, Folder 3)
  - 766-769 (Box 489, Folder 4)
  - 770-772 (Box 489, Folder 5)
  - 773 (Box 489, Folder 6)
  - 774-775 (Box 489, Folder 7)
  - 776-779 (Box 489, Folder 8)
  - 780-783 (Box 489, Folder 9)
  - 784-788 (Box 489, Folder 10)
  - 789-790 (Box 489, Folder 11)
  - 791-795 (Box 489, Folder 12)
  - 796-799 (Box 489, Folder 13)
  - 800 (Box 490, Folder 1)
  - 801-807 (Box 490, Folder 2)
  - 808 (Box 490, Folder 3)
  - 809-811 (Box 490, Folder 4)
  - 812 (Box 490, Folder 5)
  - 813-815 (Box 490, Folder 6)
  - 816.1 (Box 490, Folder 7)
  - 816.2 (Box 490, Folder 8)
  - 816.3 (Box 490, Folder 9)
  - 817-820 (Box 491, Folder 1)
  - 821-826 (Box 491, Folder 2)
  - 827-827A (Box 491, Folder 3)
  - 828 (Box 491, Folder 4)
  - 829-833 (Box 491, Folder 5)
  - 834 (Box 491, Folder 6)
  - 835 (Box 491, Folder 7)
  - 836-837 (Box 491, Folder 8)
  - 838 (Box 491, Folder 9)
  - 839-841 (Box 491, Folder 10)
  - 842-847 (Box 491, Folder 11)
  - 848 (Box 491, Folder 12)
  - 849-854 (Box 491, Folder 13)
  - 855-857 (Box 492, Folder 1)
  - 858-861 (Box 492, Folder 2)
  - 862 (Box 492, Folder 3)
  - 863 (Box 492, Folder 4)
  - 864-864A (Box 492, Folder 5)
  - 865-866 (Box 492, Folder 6)
  - 867-868 (Box 492, Folder 7)
  - 869-876 (Box 492, Folder 8)
  - 877 (Box 492, Folder 9)
  - 878 (Box 492, Folder 10)
  - 879-881 (Box 492, Folder 11)
  - 882 (Box 492, Folder 12)
  - 883 (Box 492, Folder 13)
  - 884 (Box 492, Folder 14)
  - 884A (Box 492, Folder 15)
  - 885 (Box 492, Folder 16)
  - 886 (Box 492, Folder 17)
  - 887 (Box 492, Folder 18)
  - 888-889 (Box 492, Folder 19)
  - 890 (Box 493, Folder 1)
  - 891 (Box 493, Folder 2)
  - 892-894 (Box 493, Folder 3)
  - 895 (Box 493, Folder 4)
  - 896-899 (Box 493, Folder 5)
  - 900-903 (Box 493, Folder 6)
  - 904-905 (Box 493, Folder 7)
  - 906 (Box 493, Folder 8)
  - 907 (Box 493, Folder 9)
  - 908-909 (Box 493, Folder 10)
  - 910-915 (Box 493, Folder 11)
  - 916-919 (Box 493, Folder 12)
  - 920-924 (Box 493, Folder 13)
  - 925-929 (Box 493, Folder 14)
  - 930-934 (Box 493, Folder 15)
  - 935-939 (Box 493, Folder 16)
  - 940-943 (Box 493, Folder 17)
  - 944-948 (Box 494, Folder 1)
  - 949 (Box 494, Folder 2)
  - 950 (Box 494, Folder 3)
  - 951-959 (Box 494, Folder 4)
  - 960-969 (Box 494, Folder 5)
  - 970-971 (Box 494, Folder 6)
  - 972 (Box 494, Folder 7)
  - 973-979 (Box 494, Folder 8)
  - 980-985 (Box 494, Folder 9)
  - 986 (Box 494, Folder 10)
  - 987 (Box 495, Folder 1)
  - 988 (Box 495, Folder 2)
  - 989 (Box 495, Folder 3)
  - 990 (Box 495, Folder 4)
  - 991 (Box 495, Folder 5)
  - 992 (Box 495, Folder 6)
  - 993 (Box 495, Folder 7)
  - 993A.1 (Box 496, Folder 1)
  - 993A.2 (Box 496, Folder 2)
  - 993B (Box 496, Folder 3)
  - 994-999 (Box 496, Folder 4)
  - 1000 (Box 496, Folder 5)
  - 1001 (Box 496, Folder 6)
  - 1002 (Box 496, Folder 7)
  - 1003-1004 (Box 496, Folder 8)
  - 1005 (Box 496, Folder 9)
  - 1006 (Box 496, Folder 10)
  - 1007 (Box 496, Folder 11)
  - 1008-1009 (Box 496, Folder 12)
  - 1010 (Box 496, Folder 13)
  - 1011 (Box 496, Folder 14)
  - 1012-1014 (Box 496, Folder 15)
  - 1015 (Box 496, Folder 16)
  - 1016-1017 (Box 497, Folder 1)
  - 1018-1019 (Box 497, Folder 2)
  - 1020-1021 (Box 497, Folder 3)
  - 1022 (Box 497, Folder 4)
  - 1023 (Box 497, Folder 5)
  - 1024 (Box 497, Folder 6)
  - 1025-1029 (Box 497, Folder 7)
  - 1030-1032 (Box 497, Folder 8)
  - 1033 (Box 497, Folder 9)
  - 1034-1035 (Box 497, Folder 10)
  - 1036-1037 (Box 497, Folder 11)
  - 1038-1039 (Box 497, Folder 12)
  - 1040 (Box 497, Folder 13)
  - 1041 (Box 497, Folder 14)
  - 1042-1043 (Box 497, Folder 15)
  - 1044 (Box 497, Folder 16)
  - 1045-1049 (Box 497, Folder 17)
  - 1050-1052 (Box 497, Folder 18)
  - 1053 (Box 497, Folder 19)
  - 1054 (Box 498, Folder 1)
  - 1055 (Box 498, Folder 2)
  - 1056 (Box 498, Folder 3)
  - 1057 (Box 498, Folder 4)
  - 1058-1059 (Box 498, Folder 5)
  - 1060-1061 (Box 498, Folder 6)
  - 1062 (Box 498, Folder 7)
  - 1063-1065 (Box 498, Folder 8)
  - 1066 (Box 498, Folder 9)
  - 1067 (Box 498, Folder 10)
  - 1068-1071 (Box 498, Folder 11)
  - 1072 (Box 498, Folder 12)
  - 1073-1079 (Box 498, Folder 13)
  - 1080 (Box 498, Folder 14)
  - 1081-1083 (Box 498, Folder 15)
  - 1084-1086 (Box 498, Folder 16)
  - 1087-1088 (Box 498, Folder 17)
  - 1089 (Box 498, Folder 18)
  - 1090-1091 (Box 498, Folder 19)
  - 1092.1 (Box 499, Folder 1)
  - 1092.2 (Box 499, Folder 2)
  - 1092.3 (Box 499, Folder 3)
  - 1092.4 (Box 499, Folder 4)
  - 1093-1094 (Box 499, Folder 5)
  - 1095-1097 (Box 499, Folder 6)
  - 1098-1098 (Box 499, Folder 7)
  - 1100-1102 (Box 499, Folder 8)
  - 1103 (Box 499, Folder 9)
  - 1104-1107 (Box 499, Folder 10)
  - 1108-1108A (Box 499, Folder 11)
  - 1109-1110 (Box 499, Folder 12)
  - 1111 (Box 500, Folder 1)
  - 1111A-1115 (Box 500, Folder 2)
  - 1116-1119 (Box 500, Folder 3)
  - 1120-1125 (Box 500, Folder 4)
  - 1126-1129 (Box 500, Folder 5)
  - 1130-1139 (Box 500, Folder 6)
  - 1140-1143 (Box 500, Folder 7)
  - 1144 (Box 500, Folder 8)
  - 1145-1149 (Box 501, Folder 1)
  - 1150-1153 (Box 501, Folder 2)
  - 1154.1 (Box 501, Folder 3)
  - 1154.2 (Box 501, Folder 4)
  - 1154.3 (Box 501, Folder 5)
  - 1155-1157 (Box 501, Folder 6)
  - 1158-1159 (Box 501, Folder 7)
  - 1160 (Box 502, Folder 1)
  - 1161 (Box 502, Folder 2)
  - 1162 (Box 502, Folder 3)
  - 1163-1165 (Box 502, Folder 4)
  - 1166 (Box 502, Folder 5)
  - 1167-1168 (Box 502, Folder 6)
  - 1169 (Box 502, Folder 7)
  - 1170-1171 (Box 502, Folder 8)